Jurgen Stevens

- **(**847) 802-2801

- Bridgeport, Chicago, IL 60608 ⊕ jurgenstevens.dev linkedin.com/in/jurgenstevens/

Personal Summary

Chicago-based Full Stack Software Developer with 3+ years of self taught, immersive bootcamp, and instructional experience. I want to put my programming skills to good use and be a part of something that has a beneficial impact on peoples' lives.

Education

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019 **SEI CERTIFICATION** General Assembly, Chicago, IL 500+ Hours of JavaScript, Python, Node.js, React, SQL & NoSQL.

Experience

Mar 2021 -Present

INSTRUCTIONAL ASSOCIATE | General Assembly, Chicago, IL

- I lead CSS lessons to groups of thirty or more students, as well as lessons on producing an API with Express, Mongoose, and more.
- Work closely with co-instructors or teaching assistants to provide students with meaningful, detailed and prompt feedback on their progress.
- Inspire students to persevere through challenges of learning a new skill set.
- Grade and provide detailed feedback on students' deliverables and code reviews for their unit projects.

Sept 2018 -June 2020

AUDIT DEPARTMENT TRAINER | Second Life Mac, Skokie, IL

- Trained new employees and made sure they were correctly grading used Apple products.
- Made sure that every batch of Apple products that were sent through had their memory erased and their settings reset back to factory defaults.
- Informed the warehouse manager about the status of Apple product batches on a regular basis.

Skills

LANGUAGES FRAMEWORKS TOOLS

- JavaScript
- **Python**
- HTML5
- **SQL**

- React.js
- **Express.js**
- Mongoose.js
- **Flask**
- SASS

- Node.js
- **Notion**
- Trello